<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>partitionmanager.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KDE Partition Manager</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">KDE Partitionshåndtering</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KDE Partitiebeheerder</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Gestor de Partições do KDE</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Gerenciador de Partições do KDE</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KDE Správca partícií</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">KDE:s partitionshanterare</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Редактор розділів для KDE</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKDE Partition Managerxx</name>
  <summary>Partition Editor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Partitioneringsprogram</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Partitiebewerker</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Editor de Partições</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Editor de Partições</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Editor partícií</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Partitionseditor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Редактор розділів на дисках</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxPartition Editorxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KDE Partition Manager is a utility program to help you manage the disk devices, partitions and file systems on your computer. It allows you to easily create, copy, move, delete, resize without losing data, backup and restore partitions.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">KDE Partition Manager er et værktøj til at hjælpe dig med at håndtere dine diskenheder og filsystemerne på din computer. Den lader dig nemt oprette, kopiere, flytte, slette, ændre størrelse uden at miste data, tage backup og gendanne partitioner.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KDE Partitiebeheerder is een hulpprogramma om u helpen bij het beheer van de schijven, partities en bestandssystemen op uw computer. Het stelt u in staat gemakkelijk partities te maken, te kopiëren, te verplaatsen, te verwijderen, hun grootte te wijzigen zonder verlies van gegevens en hiervan een reservekopie te maken of hier vanaf te herstellen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Gestor de Partições do KDE é um utilitário que o ajuda a gerir os dispositivos dos discos, as suas partições e sistemas de ficheiros no seu computador. Permite-lhe facilmente criar, copiar, mover, apagar, dimensionar sem perder dados, salvaguardar e repor partições.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O Gerenciador de Partições do KDE é um utilitário que o ajuda a gerenciar os dispositivos de disco, suas partições e sistemas de arquivos no seu computador. Permite-lhe facilmente criar, copiar, mover, excluir, redimensionar sem perder dados, criar backup e restaurar partições.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KDE správca partícií je nástroj, ktorý vám má pomôcť spravovať diskové zariadenia, partície a súborové systémy na vašom počítači. Umožňuje vám jednoducho vytvoriť, kopírovať, presúvať, mazať a meniť veľkosť bez straty dám, zálohovať a obnovovať partície.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Редактор розділів KDE — допоміжна програма, яку призначено для полегшення керування дисковими пристроями, розділами та файловими системами на комп’ютері. За її допомогою ви зможете без проблем створювати, копіювати, пересувати, вилучати та змінювати розміри розділів без втрати даних, створювати резервні копії розділів та відновлювати дані з цих резервних копій.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKDE Partition Manager is a utility program to help you manage the disk devices, partitions and file systems on your computer. It allows you to easily create, copy, move, delete, resize without losing data, backup and restore partitions.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Supports a large number of file systems, including ext2/3/4, btrfs, reiserfs, NTFS, FAT16/32, JFS, XFS and more</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Understøtter et større antal filsystemer, derunder ext2/3/4, btrfs, reiserfs, NTFS, FAT16/32, JFS, XFS og andre</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt een groot aantal bestandssystemen, inclusief ext2/3/4, btrfs, reiserfs, NTFS, FAT16/32, JFS, XFS en meer</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta um grande conjunto de sistemas de ficheiros, incluindo o ext2/3/4, btrfs, reiserfs, NTFS, FAT16/32, JFS, XFS entre outros</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte a um grande conjunto de sistemas de arquivos, incluindo o ext2/3/4, btrfs, reiserfs, NTFS, FAT16/32, JFS, XFS, entre outros</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podporuje veľký počet súborových systémov, vrátane ext2/3/4, btrfs, reiserfs, NTFS, FAT16/32, JFS, XFS a viac</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder ett stort antal filsystem, inklusive ext2/3/4, btrfs, reiserfs, NTFS, FAT16/32, JFS, XFS med flera</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка широкого набору файлових систем, зокрема ext2/3/4, btrfs, reiserfs, NTFS, FAT16/32, JFS, XFS тощо.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports a large number of file systems, including ext2/3/4, btrfs, reiserfs, NTFS, FAT16/32, JFS, XFS and morexx</li>
      <li>Makes use of already available external programs to get its job done</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Gør brug af allerede tilgængelige eksterne programmer til at udføre arbejdet</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Maakt gebruik van al beschikbare externe programma's om deze taken uit te voeren</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Tira partido dos programas externos já existentes para terminar a sua tarefa</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Utiliza os programas externos já existentes para terminar a sua tarefa</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Používa už existujúce dostupné externé programy na vykonanie svojej práce</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Drar nytta av redan tillgängliga externa program för att få jobbet gjort</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Використання доступних зовнішніх інструментів для виконання завдань.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxMakes use of already available external programs to get its job donexx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://sourceforge.net/projects/partitionman/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kdepartitionmanager</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/development/en/extragear-sysadmin/partitionmanager/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/kdepartitionmanager.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>partitionmanager</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
